followterry.com 2010-11-16

# How we collect and store information depends on the page you are visiting, the activities in which you elect to participate and the services provided. For example, you may be asked to provide information when you register for access to certain portions of our site or request certain features, such as newsletters or when you make a purchase. You may provide information when you participate in sweepstakes and contests, message boards and chat rooms, and other interactive areas of our site. Like most Web sites, FollowTerry.com also collects information automatically and through the use of electronic tools that may be transparent to our visitors. For example, we may log the name of your Internet Service Provider or use cookie technology to recognize you and hold information from your visit. Among other things, the cookie may store your user name and password, sparing you from having to re-enter that information each time you visit, or may control the number of times you encounter a particular advertisement while visiting our site. As we adopt additional technology, we may also gather information through other means. In certain cases, you can choose not to provide us with information, for example by setting your browser to refuse to accept cookies, but if you do you may be unable to access certain portions of the site or may be asked to re-enter your user name and password, and we may not be able to customize the site’s features according to your preferences.

                                       PRIVACY POLICY
Last Updated: 12-Sep-2006
FollowTerry.com strives to offer its visitors the many advantages of Internet technology and to
provide an interactive and personalized experience. We may use Personally Identifiable
Information (your name, e-mail address, street address, telephone number) subject to the terms of
this privacy policy. We will never sell, barter, or rent your email address to any unauthorized
third party. Period."
How we gather information from users
How we collect and store information depends on the page you are visiting, the activities in
which you elect to participate and the services provided. For example, you may be asked to
provide information when you register for access to certain portions of our site or request certain
features, such as newsletters or when you make a purchase. You may provide information when
you participate in sweepstakes and contests, message boards and chat rooms, and other
interactive areas of our site. Like most Web sites, FollowTerry.com also collects information
automatically and through the use of electronic tools that may be transparent to our visitors. For
example, we may log the name of your Internet Service Provider or use cookie technology to
recognize you and hold information from your visit. Among other things, the cookie may store
your user name and password, sparing you from having to re-enter that information each time
you visit, or may control the number of times you encounter a particular advertisement while
visiting our site. As we adopt additional technology, we may also gather information through
other means. In certain cases, you can choose not to provide us with information, for example by
setting your browser to refuse to accept cookies, but if you do you may be unable to access
certain portions of the site or may be asked to re-enter your user name and password, and we
may not be able to customize the site’s features according to your preferences.
What we do with the information we collect
Like other Web publishers, we collect information to enhance your visit and deliver more
individualized content and advertising. We respect your privacy and do not share your
information with anyone.
Aggregated Information (information that does not personally identify you) may be used in many
ways. For example, we may combine information about your usage patterns with similar
information obtained from other users to help enhance our site and services (e.g., to learn which
pages are visited most or what features are most attractive). Aggregated Information may
occasionally be shared with our advertisers and business partners. Again, this information does
not include any Personally Identifiable Information about you or allow anyone to identify you
individually.
We may use Personally Identifiable Information collected on FollowTerry.com to communicate
with you about your registration and customization preferences; our Terms of Service and

privacy policy; services and products offered by FollowTerry.com and other topics we think you
might find of interest.
Personally Identifiable Information collected by FollowTerry.com may also be used for other
purposes, including but not limited to site administration, troubleshooting, processing of e-
commerce transactions, administration of sweepstakes and contests, and other communications
with you. Certain third parties who provide technical support for the operation of our site (our
Web hosting service for example) may access such information. We will use your information
only as permitted by law. In addition, from time to time as we continue to develop our business,
we may sell, buy, merge or partner with other companies or businesses. In such transactions, user
information may be among the transferred assets. We may also disclose your information in
response to a court order, at other times when we believe we are reasonably required to do so by
law, in connection with the collection of amounts you may owe to us, and/or to law enforcement
authorities whenever we deem it appropriate or necessary. Please note we may not provide you
with notice prior to disclosure in such cases.
Affiliated sites, linked sites and advertisements
FollowTerry.com expects its partners, advertisers and affiliates to respect the privacy of our
users. Be aware, however, that third parties, including our partners, advertisers, affiliates and
other content providers accessible through our site, may have their own privacy and data
collection policies and practices. For example, during your visit to our site you may link to, or
view as part of a frame on a FollowTerry.com page, certain content that is actually created or
hosted by a third party. Also, through FollowTerry.com you may be introduced to, or be able to
access, information, Web sites, features, contests or sweepstakes offered by other parties.
FollowTerry.com is not responsible for the actions or policies of such third parties. You should
check the applicable privacy policies of those third parties when providing information on a
feature or page operated by a third party.
While on our site, our advertisers, promotional partners or other third parties may use cookies or
other technology to attempt to identify some of your preferences or retrieve information about
you. For example, some of our advertising is served by third parties and may include cookies that
enable the advertiser to determine whether you have seen a particular advertisement before.
Other features available on our site may offer services operated by third parties and may use
cookies or other technology to gather information. FollowTerry.com does not control the use of
this technology by third parties or the resulting information, and is not responsible for any
actions or policies of such third parties.
You should also be aware that if you voluntarily disclose Personally Identifiable Information on
message boards or in chat areas, that information can be viewed publicly and can be collected
and used by third parties without our knowledge and may result in unsolicited messages from
other individuals or third parties. Such activities are beyond the control of FollowTerry.com and
this policy.
Children

FollowTerry.com does not knowingly collect or solicit Personally Identifiable Information from
or about children under 13 except as permitted by law. If we discover we have received any
information from a child under 13 in violation of this policy, we will delete that information
immediately. If you believe FollowTerry.com has any information from or about anyone under
13, please contact us at the address listed below.
Contacting Us.
We can be reached by contacting:
FollowTerry.com
Email: terry@followterry.com
Changes to this Policy
FollowTerry.com reserves the right to change this policy at any time. Please check this page
periodically for changes. Your continued use of our site following the posting of changes to these
terms will mean you accept those changes. Information collected prior to the time any change is
posted will be used according to the rules and laws that applied at the time the information was
collected.
Governing law
This policy and the use of this Site are governed by Virginia law. If a dispute arises under this
Policy we agree to first try to resolve it with the help of a mutually agreed-upon mediator in the
following location: Ashburn VA. Any costs and fees other than attorney fees associated with the
mediation will be shared equally by each of us.
If it proves impossible to arrive at a mutually satisfactory solution through mediation, we agree
to submit the dispute to binding arbitration at the following location: TBD, under the rules of the
American Arbitration Association. Judgment upon the award rendered by the arbitration may be
entered in any court with jurisdiction to do so.
FollowTerry.com is controlled, operated and administered entirely within Virginia. This
statement and the policies outlined herein are not intended to and do not create any contractual or
other legal rights in or on behalf of any party.
